It's my life, it's your life, fighting for
tomorrow, go catch what you really want.
I want more, anyone more,
come on, open up the door.
It's my life, it's your life, run
like a wind, jump high, yeah, yeah.
I know you're strong, believe
you can achieve your goal.
Let's keep on going, I'll not stay.
Let's do it again, you
know what I mean, baby.
No one can make my dream come true!
Don't you feel it?
I really don't know what is
Something is testing me every day.
Hey, let's go.
Let's fly away.
I know I never wanna come back here.
Hey, let's go.
Let's fly away the great
end of the unknown rules.
Standing up, blowing up.
My dream is getting wilder.
I'm not afraid, beat me, hit me.
I will never turn around.
Another day, another chance.
You know it's never too late.
If I can do it, so can you only win out.
We can let go together,
baby, growin' a rose.
It's my life, it's your life.
Party for tomorrow, go
get what you really want.
I want more, anyone more.
Come on, open up the door.
It's my life, it's your life.
Run like a wind, jump high, yeah, yeah.
I know you're strong.
Believe you can achieve your goal.
Let's keep on going, roaring.
It's my life, it's your life.
Fighting for your eyes that I
want, but you're where it was.
I want more, anyone more,
come on, open up the gate.
It's my life, it's your life,
shine like a star to be good.
I know you're strong, just that
you can't achieve your best.
Let's keep on going out of day.
You make my day every day.
no!
Oh, my God.
Oh.
Room.
Shembles.
Oh, someone saved him.
Lucy!
Look, nobody's up there anymore.
Huh?
So is it over yet?
What just happened?
Give us an update, Guts!
Watch out! Be careful!
You've been yelling too much.
Take it easy!
I have a duty to fulfill.
The citizens are waiting!
Pathetic!
What kind of announcer am I if
I can't announce the winner?
Look, you two!
Look to the sky, Dressrosa!
Watch it fade, the birdcage,
and also, don't flamingos reign over us!
We pushed it right over!
The birdcage is gone.
Oh damn, he did it.
The sky, the sky—it's clear again.
The
view that I see may look grim,
but it's not a town that's
been torn to shreds, not to me.
me Rather, it is a land
of boundless freedom.
One of infinite potential.
Holy crap, Ola, it's really good.
Then it's true.
Be careful.
The Dressrosa Defensive War.
Two thousand wicked pirates
from the Don Quixote family.
versus the fateful warriors who
gathered here from far and wide.
Culminating in a duel between their leaders,
the warlord Don Quixote do Flamingo.
Versus the beloved gladiator, Lucy!
The winner is...
Say what?
The winner!
Pull it together, man!
Just say it!
The winner is...
It's okay, we believe in you!
You got this!
We're there already!
Halt! Who's there?
Don't call for help.
My name is Don Quixote do Flamingo.
Even if you've forgotten, I have not.
Thus I've returned to take
my place as your king.
Is there something
we've done to anger you?
What could I possibly say?
Nothing can justify this. We're done.
The kingdom is finished.
We fell right into the flamingos trap.
Witch.
You're wearing me down here.
Enunciate, please.
Listen to me, Rebecca.
You can't start crying yet.
I won't let the soldier die.
Be strong, okay?
I can promise you one thing.
I'm going to give Doflamingo
the beating of his life.
Lucy.
The winner is...
Lucy!
Thank you, Koza!
And thank you, Lucy!
We're alive!
Super!
Loopyland!
Loopy!
Robbyland!
I wasn't scared at all!
Splendid works, Sir Loopy!
Remarkable indeed!
I said it all!
You see?
Nice work, bros.
You're all heroes, too.
Don't squeeze so hard!
Every toy you see was
at one point a human.
The Commander!
Those are the little people from Tontata.
They will be fighting Doflamingo with us.
brother i don't know what's going
on but you shouldn't make a girl
cry i know i'm just a toy but i
must protect her these useless tin
eyes of mine can't even shed a
tear for her he's been fighting on
his own for a whole decade but he
never gave up and he never lost hope
you filthy pirate what did you do let
him go Rick here was the one burning
the kingdom down it wasn't me the king
would never do such a thing regardless
i'll never forget what you did for me
To a soldier this battle is a chance for
us to reclaim our freedom and to restore
the honor of our dethroned King Rick
Keep your hands offer you
have taken enough from me
The collapse of the kingdom isn't
always a tragedy for its people.
In Dressrosa, even amongst
the piles of rubble,
the citizens there shed
tears of joy and relief.
Yeah!
All right!
He really took down Dolph Lamingo!
We have freedom in Dressrosa!
He took Heron the Batman! That's right!
We're free!
Oh, yes!
I'm fine.
Where do you think you're going?
Aren't you going to finish me off?
No need. Huh?
Think we're just about
good here, don't you?
You brothers are a bunch of softies.
You wanna hear what Ace said right before
we handed his ass over to the Navy?
It was after our captain
thrashed him on Bonnaroo Island.
I'll tell ya.
Hey, hurry it up.
The clash between Straw
Hat and Doflamingo's over.
The Navy's gonna be on their way.
I know. Stop.
Did you contact the chief?
Not yet.
I've been trying to.
He's not picking up.
He only answers when he's feeling chatty.
I think you'll get a real kick out of this
once
he realized he
was to get executed.
And I remember it clearly.
He said, "Don't tell my brother."
What a dumb ass.
He had no idea.
Just how much weight his name carried.
What a naive moron that kid was.
Of course the navy would run
with that story heroically.
They brought the vile
fire fist. As to just
that's
enough.
Shut your mouth,
bastard.
All I can think about
are his final moments.
It has haunted me every single
night since the day that he died.
You don't have to tell me
because I already know.
That's right, loser cruel.
I won't let that Devil Fruit
slip out of my grasp this time.
I'd be a disgrace to my crew
if I came back empty-handed.
I'll be taking it one way or another.
Sounds like you're full of regret, huh?
What did all that status and
power get you in the end?
You couldn't even use it
to save your own brother.
Where the hell were you
when it all went down?
Were you catching some
Zs or something? Yee-haw!
You weren't there for him when he needed
you most, yet you called yourself family!
Pathetic!
I will not be weighed down
by regrets any longer!
Fire Fist!
Dammit!
I was going to leave you, but
Ace here said you deserved it.
Oh, hello, Sabo.
Where are you right now?
I noticed that Burgess
was heading towards Luffy.
Figured you'd like to know that tidbit
of info, so I've been trying to call you.
Yeah?
Well, who cares?
What?
Don't worry.
I took care of that ape already.
Huh?
Anyway, did you happen to
find the list yet, Koala?
Uh, yes, I did. Cool.
Let's call the ship and head back...
Already did! Fine.
Let's meet up with Hack underground, then.
I'm with him!
We're waiting on you! Good.
Did that jackass just hang up on me?
Please don't take it
out on me, Miss Koala.
Over here!
We found the Don Quixote family.
We've got eight executives, and I think...
Yes!
The top three as well!
Take caution!
We believe most of them
have Devil Fruit powers.
You see Prism Stone just in case.
Yes, sir!
You stay right here with me.
Okay.
Whoa!
What do you think you're doing?
Get off me!
Get yourself woman or her heart! No!
Do you know if we called
HQ yet? Where are they?
Well, actually, not yet.
Ishu instructed us to delay a bit.
Vice Admiral Maynard, the video
transponder snail is ready.
All right, let me have it.
Go grab another one and
meet with the Admiral.
And follow Isho's orders
to the letter. Sir!
Meanwhile, at the nearby Applebine Island.
This is weird!
What the hell?
I heard it's a transmission
from Dressrosa.
And it's a speech from King Doflamingo!
Oh, boy.
Report from Tres Rosa.
We're broadcasting this
important declaration
to anyone who can receive this message.
I am a more example from the Navy HQ.
The name's Maynard.
The Navy?
Report from Dressrosa.
We're broadcasting this
important declaration
to anyone who can receive this message.
Why, though?
Please take a look at
the following images.
Huh?
Are those piles of rubble?
What you see behind me is the
current state of Dressrosa!
What happened there?
Keep calm and listen carefully.
I will detail the events
that took place this
afternoon involving the
warlord Doflamingo. Ready?
Nisho, I hope you are.
We are begging you, King Rick!
It took some time for
the truth to get out!
As Muke Toys, we were unable to speak up!
No, I cannot.
Please, respect my wishes.
Even with the misunderstanding
absolved, I cannot return to the throne.
But you're the only ruler worthy
to lead, Dressrosa! He's right!
We're done with all this violence!
Please, King Rick!
We share your vision of a peaceful future!
We beg you! Hmm?
Hold your pleas.
Under pressure, the Rick
family ideals shatter.
Has that not been proven by now?
We don't care if we fall.
For the chance of being a bloodless
nation, we're happy to risk it.
We want a king who will resist wars,
and we know you're the man for the job.
That's right.
Even if it results in failure,
we'll take that chance.
Who cares if we're poor?
Just make Dressrosa a peaceful
kingdom like we used to be.
Please, King Rick, listen
to the cries of your people.
No one better suited to lead us.
As the fighting king, I'm not used to this
Huh? Elisabello?
King Rick, please return
to the palace at once.
There's a bunch of incoming calls
from our neighboring nations.
They'd like to talk!
But to me?
Well,
I took it upon myself to
get the word out to people
when I told them a King
Rick would be returning,
they all seem overjoyed.
The King of Prudence?
Surely you haven't changed that
much in a mere decade, my friends.
What happened to the old you?
The man who'd give a firm stink-eye to
anyone even thinking about waging war, huh?
They're all waiting on him.
Come back to the throne.
King of Miracles, Rick Doldo III!
Your friend's a smart
man there, King Rick.
This entire mess is Doflamingo's doing.
I would hate to see you shoulder the
responsibility alone for
the error in his judgment.
That crooked pirate was unfit to rule.
But thanks to a broken arrangement
with a bunch of convicts,
the Seven Warlords system failed you.
Sadly, Dressrosa was forced to pay
this price by the bloodstained hands.
They lost the world government.
People of the kingdom.
and members of the royal family.
On behalf of the government,
allow me to offer my
most humble of apologies.
With deep regret, we've done
you a terrible disservice.
What's this about?
Admiral Isho is actually kneeling?
I'm shocked.
Now this is wild.
The Navy works directly
under the government,
and one of their highly
respected officials?
is on the ground apologizing to King Rick.
What happened over there in Dressrosa?
The fall of the heavenly demon
was due to some pirate alliance?
Take notes!
Don't miss any details!
I've never seen anything like this before.
The false prosperity of the mighty Dressrosa,
the unsavory secrets that they held.
The downfall of Don Quixote Doflamingo,
the world's most notorious
black market broker,
and the Navy HQ Admiral
Fujitora's heartfelt prostration.
All these truths have been
freed from the birdcage,
and for better or worse,
they have been unleashed
upon the entire world.
The Navy Admiral is bowing to King Rick?
Wow, they're recording it, too.
Hey, look!
That guy's an admiral, right?
No way.
This is a big deal.
Something really nuts
happened in Dressrosa.
Please raise your head, admiral.
Come on, now.
Do you truly wish for
the world to see this?
My word, don't tell me.
Is this why you did not engage Doflamingo?
Fujitora.
It was about time the
world found out the truth.
So I took one mighty gamble and
let them do all the fighting.
It was what needed to be done.
How could we let that warlord do
whatever he pleased for all those years?
Then swoop in here and start
preaching about justice.
It doesn't sit right with me.
We can't play hero for a problem we made.
What we witnessed today was a kingdom that
came together and seized its own justice.
You should be thanking the courageous
actions of pirates, gladiators,
and your citizens.
The arduous battle is over.
I thank you all.
I know it's been difficult.
Anti-Doflamingo Force!
Little King Rick Army!
Kill, sir commander!
Your operation is now complete.
We're disbanded.
Commander!
Tank, the Navy must maintain face.
The pirates and gladiators should hide.
Take them to the palace.
The same goes for anyone without a home.
Can you do that?
It'd be my pleasure, King Rick.
So,
you're telling me that that whole
mix up with Doflamingo leaving the
Warlords was actually from some power
even higher than the lot of you?
Want to explain how
that rat Doflamingo was
able to manipulate the world to his will?
This kind of malarkey needs to end,
or else I'll be the
laughingstock of the entire Navy!
Don't pull a stunt like that ever again.
It would be wise to hold
your tongue, Admiral.
Your honor is of no
concern to us right now.
Don't get a big head.
The Navy merely acts as our public face.
Regardless, this whole affair was
placed in Cypher-Pole's hands.
Ha!
Cypher-Pole, you say?
Let's lay out the facts here.
Sounds like the Celestial Dragon's
puppet went right over your heads.
Are you all really okay with that?
Watch your insolent mouth, Sakasuki.
Got anything to say about Kuzan? Hmm?
How is someone as powerful as him allying
himself with Blackbeard of all people?
The Navy's reputation is already sullied.
That lackadaisical jackass
officially resigned.
Who he chooses to partner with has
absolutely jacked to do with us.
Five Elders! Fleet Admiral!
I have urgent news.
It's concerning the state
of the Don Quixote family.
Doflamingo has fallen.
Defeated by Straw Hat and Law's Alliance.
But in the process, Tress Rossa was
reduced to rubble completely. Huh?
That's absurd!
I see.
That damn boy.
Sir, it doesn't end there.
The broadcast transmission
that was sent from
Desrosa quickly became
the talk of every country.
There's breaking news, everybody
spreading like wildfire!
It caused chaos amongst the underworld.
Joker was defeated, your majesty—he
was the only weapon supplier we had.
We'll
announce our surrender at once.
once
The war is finally over!
But we've already paid!
We had a deal!
Joker, you slimy bastard!
The weapons are somewhere at Dressrosa!
So is the Navy Admiral.
Forget about it, man.
So our sweet devil
fruit deal fell through?
What's gonna happen to
my smile agreement, huh?
If only those meddling
punks had showed up!
Come on, Tsuru.
You didn't need to set sail.
I have this.
Took the words right out of
my mouth, Inspector General.
Well, I suppose you have been on
their trail for quite some time now.
Yes, by your orders.
Want a cracker? I'm good.
Might I suggest this?
Supreme is our special of the day.
Huh? A thief!
Get back here, you old bag!
Now where'd that old lady go?
Damn, just a kid. Where are you? Hey!
Hey, they took out Dolpholingo. Not bad.
I'm proud to call them generation mates.
High Priest Aruge!
There's somebody up here!
High Priest!
Now that's just silly.
Do you know where we are?
A remote cloud island
where no one can bother us.
Trust me when I say it's a bird.
Whoa, whoa, the cojones on them two guys.
Looks like our little pirate Pallies
are making a name for themselves.
That means we'll be glomming Caesar
for ourselves, boys, capisce?
Yes, father!
That didn't take him
long to pull ahead of us.
This is a huge triumph.
Interesting, since Doflamingo's
got connections with Kaido.
There's no way he's not
going to be pissed off.
If this was intentional, they
just outed who they're after.
One of the four emperors.
Facing the king of the
beasts himself, huh?
Well, at least our target
is different than theirs.
It saves us the hassle of
wasting manpower on them.
That still leaves
red-haired shanks all to us.
We'll be able to keep focusing on that
goal or it even traveled to Drake who
once made a name for himself by provoking
Kaido Do Flamingo killed your old man.
How'd I not know?
That's in the past now.
I bear no grudge damn dude.
You are ice cold
Why not come help us?
This needs to be reported to the big man.
And something tells me he won't be happy!
Master Kaino, you're not gonna like this.
That schmuck Joker
screwed up a good thing.
We won't be getting smiles anymore.
Don't play dumb with me, Esho.
Now you know damn well
what it means for a ranking
official to admit an
oversight on this scale!
Why didn't you think to
first report this to HQ?
If I'd followed protocol,
I have a feeling that the news would have
come out with a bit of
a different spin on it.
Huh?
Care to repeat that?
I believe the Seven Warlords
system should be abolished.
Two years ago, I was there in person
when Crocodile's ruse was exposed.
And the Navy couldn't do
a damn thing about it.
If it weren't for the
Straw Hats back then,
Alabasta would have
become a pirate nation,
just like Dressrosa is now.
But the government falsely declared
Crocodile's downfall was due to the Navy.
If only I had a higher rank back then!
I'll be damned.
Fujitora really did it.
Well done.
I remember how frustrated both of us were
after what happened back in Alabasta.
But this time, the Straw Hat's
achievement won't be covered up.
It kind of feels like
retribution for that whole mess.
I'll hand it to him.
I couldn't pull this off when
I was in the same position.
I'm completely astonished.
We've got muffins.
Shall I make some coffee?
I said astonished, not famished.
Hey, sis, we're hungry.
Starby!
You can have his share then.
Anyone want coffee?
You can't give coffee to kids, silly.
I want a muffin.
Where's Mr. Vegabunk?
I think you mean Vegabunk.
It'll take just a few more days before
we reach his lab, so hang tight, okay?
Look at that.
The captain's so good with kids.
Man, I wish I were five.
All right, enough, guys.
There's still plenty of work to do.
Yes, ma 'am.
I love it when you scold me, captain.
It's called damage
control, and it's common!
Our superiors thought those pirates would
help maintain balance in this world.
The government gave them authority,
and they made people suffer in turn.
Now you expect me to paint myself a hero,
lying about solving a
problem that we created.
This is about HQ's
credibility and dignity!
Isho, sir, I'd be careful!
Your egocentric actions have caused our
system of justice to lose all face today!
If your face is all you care about,
then you should try a little
harder to keep it clean.
If admitting to a wrongdoing
means your trust is gone,
then I'd say you never had
any in the first place, sir!
You are going to clean this
entire disaster up, Fujitara.
You will not set foot in
any naval base in the entire
world until you bring me
Straw Hat and Law's heads.
You understand?!
Fine by me.
That's just what I wanted.
I want some meat.